To train for Microsoft 365 administrator you would definitely want to create a Microsoft 365 tenant.
So this tenant will give you the opportunity to land a Microsoft 365 asset administrator.
So we have different tenants you can create with how they eat, treat, try out tenant or the E5 trial tenant.
Or mine new, this tenant can also, this trial tenant can also be converted into a paid tenant.
So that creating this tenant, you have the opportunity to add some extra free license.
For example, we have the Microsoft Intune license which you can also add to your tenant or the Microsoft 365.
Because you can see that's what an Office 365 E5.
So you can add the Microsoft 365 E5 trial subscription to your tenant.
So let's get started.
So first of all, this is actually Google, start Google and tap the Microsoft 365 E5 trial or E3 trial.
You can see we have the Office 365 Enterprise Solution.
So if I click on the E5, you can see it's going to take me to this link here.
Where we can see we can set totally by now all we can just go for a free trial.
So if I go for a free trial, you can see I have open a link here.
We have the E3 trial or we have the E5 trial.
But my view, you can see here what it's actually saying.
It says, add up to 25 users during trial.
The free trial will be automatically converted to a paid and more subscription after one month.
So it means you have the option to actually stop your subscription.
So what we need to do right now is, I just want to actually, first of all, enter my email address to see if
I can't really go ahead and create this trial account.
So let me just click next.
First of all, it says, it looks like you need to create a new account.
So I'm going to click just click set up account.
So by setting up account, it's going to actually just fill in here.
You can see we have my first name, my last name.
And then you can fill your phone number which is totally not mandatory.
And then we have the company name.
Of course that is very fun.
There it is.
So I'm going to enter the phone, go, global.
And here it says, the size of the company, let me just put between 10 to 24.
And then my control I leave is I totally Belgium.
So I'm just going to scroll up here and select Belgium for my location.
And then we can now click.
So just make sure that all the information you enter are well correct.
So let's just click next.
Also, it's as well as actually asking me to provide my phone number.
So I'm just going to enter my phone number and then click next.
So right now, I'm going to actually just send, allow the Microsoft or semi verification code,
which will then allow me to continue to my subscription.
So let me just click send verification code.
So let me just pause this video and check what code that has been sent to me.
So I just enter my code and I can just hit verify.
So by clicking verify, you can see that my code has been verified.
So right now, we don't need to italic create it domain name.
You can see that domain name is going to be dot on Microsoft dot com.
I'm just going to leave it at call global.
Well, mind you, I can decide to actually change.
For example, I want to actually leave it at, let me just select kill dot john scene.
And then if I click save, it's going to check if this name is available to see if I can actually use that name.
You can see it's kel dot john scene at kel global dot on Microsoft dot com.
So now I need to actually entire password.
And then confirm that password again.
So now I will now click next.
So let's try to create my account and simply do not refresh this page.
So I'll refresh the page because if not you may lose all your information.
So let us wait for this account to be created.
And here we go.
You can see it says the quantity is utterly one.
And that is utterly the payment.
This is a five trial.
Well, mind you, you can see this maximum 25 off of 25 drain trial.
So what we need to do next is to just to add the click add payment method.
And I thought I didn't permit method, then we can now click totally save and then finish to continue to a subscription.
So now you can see that I've just added my free free trial.
And then it's utterly warning me that I should actually cancel my free trial before the end of March.
If not of the chat, this specific amount for just one license.
So what I need to do is just click start trial.
So here you can see that I totally need to verify my credit card for me to be able to use to try to continue.
So let me just verify my credit card and then just click continue.
So after you successfully verify your payment, then now you can now click go to add me center.
You can see it turns for choosing the office 3c5 if five trial.
So now let's go to the admin set.
So here you can see this is the tenant which was the Microsoft 3c5 tenant which was created.
And that's all I am office.com.
So what we need to do is go to add me center.
And from the Microsoft 3c5 admin center, we can now go to buildings.
So not building, you can go to your product.
And yeah, you're going to see the product you just activated during the free trial.
Here we go.
You can see that the address office 3c5 if I trial account, we just added and have about 25 quantity.
But we can decide to say okay, I want to add some extra services to read.
So let's go to purchase services.
And from the purchase services, we can decide to see well, let me just set for Microsoft 3c5 if five and hit enter.
So yeah, you can see we have the Microsoft 3c5 if five and also we have the Microsoft 3c5 if five, eat, discover and audit.
We have the Microsoft 3c5 if five months, two months.
So at this moment, I can decide to see well, I want to actually just click on details.
And right now you can see it says select building frequency, but I can decide to go for the trial.
Because the Microsoft 3c5 if five contains the following, you can see we have, for example, something like the Azure Active Directory.
The Microsoft Intune Cloud App Security Azure Information Protection and lost more.
And the Office 3c5 does not actually have the Microsoft Intune Azure Active Directory Cloud App Security.
So what I can actually do right now is to just click start free trial.
So I'm going to enter my telephone number, which of course I'm from Belgium.
Let me just select my telephone number.
So enter your number, just hit test me.
And you're going to receive a test code notification code message which you're going to enter.
Or let me just see, I think I received the notification code.
And then click start your free trial.
So I think the code was not correct.
Well, it says confirm your code.
And let me just try now.
Well, you see your confirmation number is does my confirmation number and I can now click continue.
So if I go back again to billing and I go back to your products.
So now you can see that I now have two products of Microsoft 3c5 if I have trial and the Office 3c5 if I have trial.
So you can, as you may remember, when I created this account, it was entirely renewed and it's going to be a paid license.
So what I cannot do is the following.
I can decide to just click on the Office 3c5 if I have trial.
And here I can decide to cancel my subscription.
And I can just click one of this within and then cancel my subscription.
So what I'm doing right now is to stop me.
For example, I forgot to actually cancel my subscription when the times were after one month that I'm not actually forced to stop paying for a subscription I'm not using.
So if I go back again to your products, you cannot see that this has been disabled and I have an active Microsoft 3c5 if I have trial, which of course is paid.
This is not available, but I can still use it.
So what I can do right now is to assign a license to Kelvin Johnson.
So if I go to my users, active users, here we have Kelvin Johnson, because you can see it's Kelvin Johnson has one license, which of course the license is no more valid.
So they just click manage products.
And then I can decide to assign this license to Kelvin and then click save changes.
So this is how you create it tenant and then add subscription or add some extra services to your Microsoft 3c5 tenant.